[dramatic music]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
- [whooshing]
- [ethereal chiming]
- [soft clattering]
- [thud]
[ethereal whooshing
and explosion]
- [ethereal music]
- [buzzing]
- [thunder rumbling]
- [rain spattering]
[snarling in the distance]
[growling in the distance]
[snarling continues]
[ominous music]
[thudding]
[man 1]
Good to go.
Charlie Oscar. Charlie Oscar.
Snakebite. how copy? Over.
[static]
-Charlie Oscar. Charlie Oscar.
Snakebite. how copy? Over.
-[growling in the distance]
[static]
They gotta be monitoring.
Crack the whip!
[man 2 speaks indistinctly]
[thunder rumbling]
Oh!
Charlie Oscar. Charlie Oscar.
Snakebite. how copy? Over.
-[radio static]
-[Jericho on radio]
Charlie Oscar Six.
- give me the latest.
- Six. it's Snakebite.
Mission's a bust.
Four down hard.
Requesting emergency extract
from Site Delta. Over.
- [snarling]
- Is the mission complete?
[loudly] Six. be advised.
we cannot continue the mission!
We are down to two!
I say again. we are down
-to two back...
-[gunshot]
[man 2 screaming]
- [growling]
- [gunshots]
- [screaming continues]
- [dramatic music]
[shouts] Where are you?
[roaring]
- [shouts]
- [gunshots]
[grunts. pants]
[panting and shakily breathing]
- [growling]
- [gasps]
- [panting]
- [roaring]
- [music increases]
- [shouts] You motherfuckers!
- [gunshots]
[shouting]
[crunching]
[echoing snarling]
["Fortunate Son
(Fogerty's Factory Version)"
by John Fogerty]
[whirring]
[engines rumbling]
I take you boys
ain't from around here.
Well. we could tell ya.
but. you know?
- [laughs] I hear that.
- ♪♪ ...when the band
Plays Hail to the Chief ♪♪
- ♪♪ Ooh. they point
The cannon at you. Lord ♪♪
- [indistinct chatter]
♪♪ It ain't me. it ain't me ♪♪
♪♪ I ain't
No senator's son. no! ♪♪
♪♪ It ain't me. it ain't me ♪♪
♪♪ I ain't no fortunate one ♪♪
♪♪ Some folks are born
Silver spoon in hand ♪♪
♪♪ Lord. don't they help
Themselves. yeah ♪♪
♪♪ But when the taxman
Come to the door ♪♪
♪♪ Lord. the house looks like
A rummage sale. yeah ♪♪
♪♪ It ain't me. it ain't me ♪♪
♪♪ I ain't no millionaire's son ♪♪
♪♪ No ♪♪
♪♪ It ain't me. it ain't me ♪♪
♪♪ I ain't no fortunate one. no ♪♪
-[man 1] Let's go...
-[indistinct chatter]
[man 2] I need three guards
to cover that jeep
right now. let's go.
[indistinct chatter continues]
[flies buzzing]
[man 3]
Fan out! Fan out!
You two. I want you both
up on that ridge ASAP.
- Yes. sir.
- Jesus fucking Christ.
We're looking
for a Major Wallace.
That'd be me.
Listen. you fuckers!
You gonna tell me
where the rest of your stash is.
-Yeah?
-[man 4 yelling in the distance]
Tell me where it's at!
Bill Wallace.
S-2. First Field Force.
- [helicopter blades whirring]
- You guys must be the field reps
- I was told to expect.
- So. where is it. Major Wallace?
Just when I thought
I'd seen it all.
Follow me.
- [indistinct chatter]
- You guys are what? CORDS?
MACV? SOG?
- CIA?
- Need to know. Major.
Right. And I clearly
don't need to know.
If you told me. you'd have to...
- That's the drill.
- [woman wailing]
- Sergeant Jensen.
- [man 5] Let's go. let's go.
- Let's go to the...
- Would you please get
this kid a lollipop.
or a shot of morphine.
- or something?
- [speaking in Vietnamese]
For Christ's sake. mama's son.
what is your problem?
I told you. I don't understand
a fucking word you say!
- [Jensen] Okay. come with me.
- She said a demon
took her husband.
- A feathered demon.
- That's what I heard.
-You speak gook?
-A little.
Comes with the territory.
Yeah. We can have
that territory.
- Truck's over here.
- [cross talk]
[ominous music]
[soft whirring]
Same barrels. Russian markings.
Knew it. What are they for?
- Right.
- [whirring]
[sighing] Oh. shit.
[whirring increases]
-I need to know about that.
My men are out...
-We're done here.
Major. and so are you.
[man 6]
Sir. Six-Alpha is on the phone.
Charlie Oscar.
Rampage. how copy?
I need to talk to the Six.
-[static]
-[man 7 on radio]
Wait one. Rampage.
Rampage. Charlie Oscar Six.
What do you got?
One truck. ten barrels.
all with standard markings.
Measure 3.46 on the counter.
Hot as hell. Over.
The NBA driver
is showing early symptoms
of radiation poisoning.
This is number five
since we've started the track.
Yeah. a... any further word
on Snakebite?
Negative.
We overflew both last knowns.
Nothing but bush and more bush.
All right. big army
is gonna come in
and extract all those civilians.
You just stay tight.
Lock it down and stand by.
- [whooshing]
- [explosions]
- [Wallace shouting] Let's go!
- We're close. I think
-we can pick up
Snakebite's track...
-No. no. no.
n... no. no. Negative.
That is. uh. too much
of a risk out there.
We are ass-deep
in alligator right now. okay?
We're just gonna mark our time
and... until I figure
this thing out. all right?
Charlie Oscar Six out.
[clatter]
[man 8]
R4 800.
Make sure Bravo gets out
of the perimeter.
What's the latest on Vulture?
[dramatic tone]
[rain spattering]
[ominous music]
[thunder rumbling]
[men speaking in Vietnamese]
- [thud]
- [groans]
- [blade rings]
- [muffled groaning]
- [grunts]
[softly] All right.
let's rock and roll.
- [indistinct chatter]
- [laughter]
[thunder rumbling]
[Baker]
Go. go!
Get down. get down.
Go. go. go!
[Keyes]
All right. Here we go. Logan.
[men speaking in Vietnamese]
- [gunshots]
- [indistinct shouting]
[thudding]
- Clear! Go!
- [indistinct shouting
in the distance]
[gunshots]
- [loud explosion]
- [yelling]
[groaning]
- [man 1] Clear!
- [gunshots continue]
Rig it!
[loud explosion]
[Leon]
Sarge. Vulture overwatch.
[man 2]
Touching!
Covering!
Vulture overwatch.
you got eyes on this circus.
Roger that. Got a visual.
Clear to engage. Over.
[gunshots in the distance]
- [gunshot]
- [Logan pants]
Twelve o'clock.
[gunshot]
Eleven o'clock. left hut.
[Logan]
Breathe. Relax.
- Aim. Squeeze.
- [gunshot]
- [gunshots]
- [explosions]
[indistinct shouting]
[gunshot]
He's toast. man.
Breathe. Relax.
- [somber music]
- [softly] Aim. Squeeze.
Vulture Six.
clean house here. man.
We're good to go. All right.
- All right.
- Just give me a second. okay?
- [exhales deeply]
- You're good.
[rain spattering]
Son of a bitch.
- [grunts]
- [Leon] Bingo.
Covering.
- Jesus fucking God.
- [Baker] Oh. no...
- [man 3] Hey.
- [Baker] Leon!
Hang in there.
We got you. we got you.
[Leon]
We got you.
Vulture Overwatch.
two friendlies
on the north side perimeter.
Call the birds and then join us.
[Leon]
Watch out!
- [yells]
- [thudding]
- [blade ringing]
- [Baker] Hey. Sergeant.
find anything?
We checked all the other huts.
No joy. Looks like these
two are all we gonna get.
We'll take it.
We'll get you outta here.
fellas.
Get you back to your families.
- [speaks indistinctly]
- [sighs] Oh.
- Too late.
- [Baker] Easy. easy...
- Fuck.
- Shit. man. You're bleeding.
Ah. shit.
- [helicopter blades whirring]
- Fuck. man.
[music increases]
[Baker]
We going home. boys.
Vodkas and T-bones for everyone.
- Yeah!
- Courtesy of your favorite
Uncle Samantha.
Oh. yeah!
And the rocks pretty
crew from Vulture Squad.
- Whoo!
- Look after him!
- [man 4] ...going home.
- Get some beers.
- boys. We earned it.
- [man 5] Oh...
[cross talk]
- Yeah. you found me.
- New order. Sarge.
Supposed to get you
and your guys
loaded into the Huey
-and out to the sea...
-Wait. wait. wait.
Who the fuck ordered this?
Some colonel named Jericho.
All I know. Sarge.
Well... [sighs and sniffs]
we're not getting any beer.
- ["Time Has Come Today"
by The Chambers Brothers]
- [man 6] Ah. shit.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
[cross talk]
- Who the fuck is Jericho?
- [laughing]
[helicopter blades whirring]
♪♪ Time has come today ♪♪
[muted]
♪♪ Young hearts
Can go their way ♪♪
♪♪ Can't put it off another day ♪♪
♪♪ I don't care what others say ♪♪
♪♪ They say
We don't listen anyway ♪♪
- ♪♪ Time has come today ♪♪
- [man speaking
indistinctly on PA]
♪♪ Hey ♪♪
♪♪ Oh! The rules
Have changed today ♪♪
- ♪♪ Hey ♪♪
- ♪♪ I have no place to stay ♪♪
- ♪♪ I'm thinking
About the subway ♪♪
- ♪♪ Hey ♪♪
- Jesus!
You recons look like
a sack of hampered assholes.
- Where's Baker?
- What are you doin' here?
More importantly.
what are we doin' here?
Because we all made
some poor life choices. Baker.
The old man would love
to discuss
the consequences with you.
No rest for the weary.
- Miller. get that arm
checked out.
- Whatever.
I'm good. Sarge.
- I ain't asking!
- ♪♪ Time has come today ♪♪
- ♪♪ Time ♪♪
- [indistinct chatter]
♪♪ Time ♪♪
- Hey.
- ♪♪ Time ♪♪
- Sir.
- I heard you got two.
Nice work. Baker.
It is not bad
for a sorry ass LURP team.
Yeah. yeah. Well.
you gotta remember.
I let you choose that team
of degenerates and fuckups.
so. you know.
maybe you were right after all.
Yeah. you gotta be a lunatic
if you're gonna be a Vulture.
Well. maybe so. but I'm
gonna tell you something.
[indistinct chatter]
Let's see what you guys think
of this next mission.
- Sir.
- Mm-hmm.
[chuckles]
Have a seat. everybody.
Smoke 'em if you got 'em.
- There he is. Razor.
- [growls softly]
[clears throat] There we go!
You hungry there. Razor?
-[growling]
-Oh. man. I bet you are!
You deserve it.
I got so much respect
for this guy. You know why?
Because he doesn't beg
like a little fucking dog.
He's an apex predator.
top of the food chain.
[indistinct muttering]
Took on a whole platoon
of my men and it wasn't
even scared.
Now it's sitting in there.
he's all chained up.
and he's waiting
for an alpha male to feed him.
And so it goes.
RT Vulture.
Yeah. you did one shit hot job
on that POW snatch.
Brought two live ones back.
We ain't seen that yet
this side of the Z.
By the way. you managed to do it
without even pissing me off.
- First time
for everything. Colonel.
- [laughter]
Yeah. nothing succeeds
like success.
Y'all ready for your next
kick-ass mission?
[sighs] Bring it on. Colonel.
All RT Vulture needs
is an Indige rucksack
and half a shoulder
to carry it on.
Yeah. maybe bring it on
after a night's sleep. Colonel.
You got it.
Zero dark thirty.
we're gonna drop you
in right here.
Three days ago.
we sent a MIC team in here.
ODA 225 at Van Gent.
They were sent over here
to investigate
some heavy lift transports.
new. uh. construction bunkers
and that sort of shit.
Green beanies get
lost in all that bush. huh?
- Leon.
- They did not get lost.
Radio fucking silence
and we could see nothing
from the air.
There is something
going on out there
in that valley.
Y'all are LURPs. right?
Reconnaissance is
your fucking business.
Let's get after it.
What's the end game. Colonel?
Assuming we find 'em.
do we round 'em up.
-call for extraction?
-That is negative.
I need you to find 'em.
identify 'em. call it in.
We'll take care of extraction.
And what's so special
about this valley. sir?
Fuckin' new guy.
Classified.
Seems kinda Major League
for trolleys. sir.
- Sounds more like NBA.
- [soft chuckling]
Or PLA. you know. right?
We can theorize
about that shit forever.
Y'all stay in your fucking lane.
Keep your head
on a fucking swivel...
- [continues indistinctly]
- And what is it exactly
the Green Berets
were looking for. sir?
- [thud]
- Fuckin' new guy.
Classified. motherfucker!
Hey. fucking classified.
all right?
I got moisturizer
that's older than you.
you little fucking bitch.
Here's what the fuck I want.
I lost my fucking Green Berets
and I need y'all
to find 'em for me.
- Vultures will find 'em. sir.
- All right. we're gonna
come back here
for a meeting at 18:30.
Y'all check all your gear.
and you come back here
rested and ready to go.
That's it. Get the fuck out.
[light somber music]
- [laughs]
- [Leon] Fucking classified.
- [Jericho] Baker.
- [Baker] Sir.
I'm gonna need you
to stick around
- for another minute.
- [indistinct chatter]
[Baker]
What's the rest
of the story. Colonel?
Are you... thinking
we might find a bunch
of SF corpses out there?
You go out there and you find me
something. all right?
And you let me worry
about the rest of it.
I'll come up with it.
don't you worry.
- [sighs] That's
pretty thin. sir.
- [Jericho] Well.
you go out there
and you get me
a detailed report.
That's all I ask.
And you make sure
that none of these fuckups.
all right.
these loose cannons of yours.
they don't try to play hero.
All right?
Now. are we tracking on that?
Can you at least tell me
what they were looking for?
[chuckles softly] Classified.
Take this seriously.
and I'll take a big eraser
to that 201 file.
All those allegations
that you had with McNeil...
I believed in you
during that investigation.
I was in your corner.
That's why I had you
transferred over to LURPs.
All right?
I appreciate that. sir.
[light tense music]
Just keep these fuckups in line.
that's all I ask.
Dismissed.
[indistinct chatter]
[engine rumbling]
[indistinct chatter].
Yes. Sarge.
You don't need a poncho.
Makes too much noise.
And break down
the C-ration boxes.
If it's bulk or excess weight.
shit can happen.
LURPs write the wrong rules.
I guess.
There it is. compadre.
Carry only what you need.
If you can't carry it
in a pocket or a liner.
you don't need it. man.
But this...
you most definitely need.
[blade rings]
Got some loco dudes
on this team.
I knew what I sign up for
when I volunteered
comin' over here.
Listen. man.
Baker picked you for a reason.
It's his reason and he knows
what he needs in the Vulture.
Must figure you have
what it takes.
Best thing you can do
is prove him right.
[indistinct chatter]
Yes. Sergeant.
[man]
just little more right here.
Get those to the squad.
[whistling]
[gentle music playing]
[Leon]
Whoo!
Here's your canteens.
It's fucking pissing down there.
[Miller]
It's always pissing. man.
[exhales sharply]
[chuckles] How's the arm?
Oh. it's fine.
What you got there. bro?
- [sloshing]
- Oh. this...
is a sacred libation.
- I found this hooch.
- Oh. damn. Where'd you get it?
Them two spooks.
they had it in their tent.
Figured they went out
there blowing bush
and trading rounds
with the gooks. so.
I rate good stateside hooch
more than they do.
This shit any better
than what they cook up at home?
No. it doesn't even compare
to Smoky Mountain bust head.
- but it'll do in a pinch. Hmm?
- Ah.
You remember you dragging
your drunken ass
out of that mess?
No. I was drunk.
- [clack]
- But I owe you. if that helps.
Oh. what helps is you not
getting so shitfaced at camp
you can't see straight
on the next mission.
I'd seen what was waiting
for us on the other side.
Hence why I don't feel bad
taking this here hooch
as an advance payment.
Squid pro and sh... shit.
Quid pro quo. Jesus Christ. Eli!
Don't try to sound intelligent
or you're gonna lose that charm
we all love.
Why don't you shut that
mouth of yours for once. Keyes?
Relax. compadre.
Or you're gonna miss out
on all these presents
I got here.
- Since Miller here has found
the Good Book...
- Mm. Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna excuse him
from the. uh.
- embarrassment of the Lord.
- [Eli laughs]
- [Miller] Wow.
- Ho. ho. ho. buddy.
-[chuckles mockingly]
Huh. ho. ho.
-[Eli laughs]
You wanna work on your charm?
Follow Keyes. man.
This man can sell ice
to Eskimos.
Must've buttered up
some assistant to the colonel
to find these out here.
- [Eli] Buttered it up
and slipped it in.
- Mm-hmm!
Oh. man. I learned
from the best.
[laughs] This better
have tits in it.
- Well...
- [Miller laughs]
All right! The new guy.
[indistinct chatter]
You got
the most important choice
you're ever gonna make.
- What's that?
- Candy for your eyes...
or...
- candy for your mouth.
- [helicopter blades whirring]
What's it gonna be?
- I'll take the mouth candy.
- [Eli] Wrong answer.
[Miller] You ever seen
a naked woman. man?
[Eli sighs]
- Does your mother count?
- [Miller laughs] Oh. shit.
- New guy's got some balls.
- Oh. Come on. man.
Cut the shit. all right?
New guy just made an honest
and... truthful answer.
and we should respect that.
- Wrong fucking choice though.
- [laughter]
- New guy's a moron.
- [laughter continues]
That means... this is for you.
Oh. What would happen
to this club without you?
- Huh?
- [sighs]
Probably all kill each other.
- [chuckles]
- Uh. Logan. man. uh.
hey. we gotta talk.
You wanna break up?
[chuckles] No.
Uh. it's about. um.
- what happened on the hilltop.
- Yeah.
I'm... I'm... I'm serious. man.
You gotta... you gotta talk
to somebody about this shit.
-Man...
-U... um. there's...
There's no range coaches
out there. man.
You can shoot
without chanting all that...
- fucking brass bullshit.
- I can't help it. Keyes.
The voices are in my head
all the time.
But if I say 'em out loud.
it helps me stay on target.
-Yeah. All right.
[chuckles] Okay.
-Yeah.
But it's gonna get
your dumb ass killed.
Look... I don't wanna see
that happen.
So you promise me.
when we get back to the rear.
you talk to somebody about this.
All right?
Sure. I'll see somebody.
[indistinct shouting
in the distance]
Assuming we even
make it back to the rear.
[laughs]
I see the boys
are corrupting you.
Good.
Team brief in ten mikes.
All hands in the briefing tent.
- [claps]
- Yeah. boss!
Gonna be some embarrassed
Green Berets
when we pull their asses
out of there.
- [Miller] Fuck yeah.
- [laughing]
- [helicopter blades whirring]
- [dramatic music]
The fuck is that?
- [beeping]
- That's weird.
What's up?
The equipment's all screwy.
We're still
flying right. though.
We're coming up
on datum point zero.
Skids down in one mike!
One mike! One mike!
One mike!
Whoo!
[indistinct chatter]
[pilot]
Good luck. Vultures.
Gear up.
What was that cutting a path
through the trees
back over there?
Looks like a game trail.
but bigger than I've ever seen.
- Elephants?
- Some fucking
big elephants. Sarge.
- The enemy still uses them.
- Fuck. I can't
understand Jericho.
Would've something about that
instead of talking about
a stupid goddamn tiger
the whole time.
Ah. Jericho's shit
is fucked up. man.
- You cannot trust
that motherfucker.
- [Baker] Cut the shit.
Whatever dinky-di Phoenix
number he's running.
don't mean nothin'.
We got our job.
find those Green Berets.
- Fan out!
- [crickets chirping]
[suspenseful music]
[ominous tone]
[Leon]
What is it?
Track.
[Leon]
Is it our guys?
No. Animal.
Something big.
It's a big bird.
Ostrich. emu. maybe a cassowary.
I studied 'em.
There's another one right there.
[clicks]
Let's backtrack 'em. Leon.
They're weird enough.
I could absolutely see
the green beanies tracking 'em.
- What do you got?
- Jack shit.
Just these big ass
Liberace feathers.
Leon. you ever see
something like this?
No. Never.
- What do you got?
- Yeah. I got a backpack.
Xavier?
Piles of shit. Big piles.
- Don't look at me.
- No. Like guano. but.
but huge.
[music continues]
[Baker]
Sergeant.
Make sense of that.
[Xavier]
There's a mark here that says
"Research Station Four."
Maybe where they were headed.
Was there anything else
around the pack?
[Logan]
Yeah. 5.56 casings.
5.56?
[Logan]
Yeah. And footprints.
Yeah. uh. two different
kinds of tracks.
US Army issue size tens
and some other shit.
Oh. and it look like struggle.
[ominous music]
[distant screeching]
We follow those tracks
for a klick or two.
- You're on point.
- You got it. boss.
- [Miller] Sir.
- [indistinct chatter]
[crickets chirping]
[grumbling in the distance]
[growling in the distance]
- [growling]
- [sighs]
- [growling and screeching]
- [leaves rustling]
- [twigs snapping]
- Oh. shit.
[growling and screeching
increase]
[leaves rustling]
[gasps]
[breathes heavily]
[softly] Rock apes.
- Fucking things are
all over these hills.
- [panting]
[Logan]
That ain't
no fucking rock apes. man.
- [growling]
- Well. fuck.
[Baker]
Time out. Keep moving.
Whatever that is.
it's moving in this direction.
[growling continues]
[breathes shakily]
[soft growling]
- [screeching]
- [Baker screams]
[Leon shouts]
Something's got Baker!
[screaming]
[grunts]
- [gunshots]
- [roaring]
[screeching]
[footsteps receding]
[Baker grunts]
- [Xavier] Baker!
- [Leon] Sarge!
- [grunting]
- I found him. he's down here!
-I found him! Sarge...
-[Xavier] Is he okay?
- What is that shit?
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- [Leon] That thing looked huge.
- [groans]
- [Xavier] Anyone seen
where it went?
- [groans]
- Fucked if I know. man.
- Could be anywhere now.
- Don't let the shadows
play tricks on you.
Whatever it was. let's get
some distance between us.
- It might not be
that simple. Sarge.
- Why not?
It wasn't scared of us.
And if it's hungry.
it wouldn't be scared
to come back either.
We gotta get out
of its territory.
How much territory
are we talking?
If it's a tiger.
60 square miles.
That's this whole
fucking valley. man.
Yeah! So quit your bitching
and get a hump at it.
You heard what the
colonel said about tigers.
[Xavier] Yeah.
Great length.
But that ain't no tiger.
-Yeah. no shit.
-It's nothing we can't handle.
Let's move.
I wanna get
to that research station
before dawn.
Let's hump it.
[growling in the distance]
[speaking in Russian]
[Tolstoy in Russian accent]
Borodin's orders are
to track the Americans.
We engage only if they approach
one of our facilities.
Con Nhen. lead the way.
[in Russian accent]
Such friendly people.
Only been here a week.
and I wish I could stay forever.
-[in Vietnamese accent]
Your bones will.
-[growling in the distance]
[suspenseful music]
Con Nhen. you need to relax.
How do you know if Russian
was telling you a joke?
[crickets chirping]
'Cause they will say. is joke.
Still warm.
Can you pick up the trail?
[branch breaks]
[ominous tone]
Still may be close.
Spread out. Do not engage.
Be lower than the grass.
Be quieter than water.
Yeah. The Americans are pussies.
-We should just...
-Be quiet. Spread out
and keep moving.
[softly] Stupid kid.
Stupid country.
Stupid mosquitoes.
- [growls]
- [groans]
- [snapping]
Tolstoy! Aleksandr's gone.
His riffle's filled with blood.
Are any of your people out here?
- What's so funny?
- Follow the blood trail.
- [gun rattles]
- Go.
[coughs and groans]
- What is it?
- [Tolstoy] Don't look.
What is Tolstoy looking at?
I need to see him.
Let me s...
[ominous music]
[retches and vomits]
We need to find
all the Americans
and kill them all.
Con Nhen. Tolstoy. He's dead.
Let's go.
[music increases]
[growling and screeching
in the distance]
[breathing heavily]
[crickets chirping]
Clear that hole. Keyes.
See what you can find in there.
[Keyes]
Yeah. all right.
What the hell do we think
that was back there?
Heard some Aussies in Phuoc Tuy
talking about gook spooks
stalking them
through the boonies.
Yeah. It was a couple gooks
in a turkey suit
- dragging the sarge. [laughs]
- [chuckles]
I could see that.
Could be some...
unknown species.
I'm telling you guys...
- [suspenseful music]
- [screech in the distance]
there's monsters out here.
[scoffs]
[snarling in the distance]
- Baker.
- [Baker] Yeah.
[Eli]
We could call it in right now.
Say we didn't find shit.
We can all go home.
[softly] Tunnel goes on forever.
Probably to the other side.
For what it's worth.
I think we're going
the right way.
We go through.
You're on point.
- Miller.
- Sarge.
[Baker]
Ass in the tunnel.
[Miller]
Ah. ass in again.
I swear to God.
Fuck him.
[ominous music]
[loud breathing]
- [gasps]
- [dramatic tone]
[flies buzzing]
[whispering] Son of a bitch.
[growling]
[dramatic music]
[screeches]
- Contact rear!
- [gunshots]
[screeching continues]
- [man 1] Fall back! Move!
- [man 2] Fall back!
[all]
Move! Move! Move!
-[man 3] Go! Come on!
Move. move. move!
-[cross talk]
- [gunshots continue]
- [screeching continues]
Move! Company. light 'em up!
[gunshots]
[man 3]
Clear! Clear!
[man 4]
On your left!
- [man 5] Come up.
- [Xavier] Fall back! Move.
[indistinct shouting]
- [screeching]
- [Xavier] Fall back!
[Baker]
Leon! Leon.
we gotta go this way!
[grunts] Leon!
[Leon shouts]
We lost the other guys.
Sarge! What do we do?
Now. let's kill
these fuckers first!
- Come on!
- [Leon] We gotta go this way.
- [growling]
- [Miller] Hey!
[music continues]
- [screeching]
- We walked
into a fucking nightmare!
Jesus fucking Christ!
[Keyes shouts]
I see an exit. now. let's go!
Baker's missing!
Keep falling back!
- Come on. let's go!
- [Keyes] Logan. come on. man!
- [Xavier] Let's go! Right now!
- [indistinct shouting]
- Fuck you!
- [explosion]
[screeching echoes
in the distance]
[suspenseful music]
- I think we're clear.
- We ain't gonna post up here.
They'll be coming.
[crickets chirping]
Fuck.
Now what?
- The hell were those things?
- [screeching]
- Oh. fuck.
- [growling]
Climb. Climb. now.
Questions later.
[grunting]
Move it!
[dramatic music]
- Shit... no! [grunting]
- [Leon] Sarge!
[growling]
[gunshots]
- [grunting]
- [screeching]
[snarling]
[panting]
Light.
[grunting] Fuck.
Suppose those things
got the other guys?
Not unless they're bulletproof.
[suspenseful music]
Son of a bitch.
That trail. right over there.
Looks like the same one
we saw coming in earlier.
Yeah. it does.
We should see where it leads.
[crickets chirping]
This is really fucked up. man.
Did the colonel tell you
these fucking things
were out here?
When we link up
with the other guys.
we jump on the radio
and ask Jericho point-blank.
I tell you one thing.
this ain't no fucking recon
looking for a bunch
of lost SF dudes.
Leon. if we want answers.
we're gonna have
to go find 'em ourselves.
[growling in the distance]
I can't believe
I fucking volunteer
for this shit.
- [panting]
- [indistinct muttering]
[screeching in the distance]
- Oh. shit.
- [screeching continues]
- [rustling]
- [growling]
Something's in here. man.
[snarling]
[whispering]
We're fucking surrounded.
Remember I told you
about the voices?
These voices. they're real.
they're real. man.
I'm telling you
they're fucking real.
- I told you.
- [Xavier] Hold your fire.
Baker and Leon
could still be out there.
- [screeching]
- [gasping]
[crickets chirping]
[sighs] Pussies.
[growling]
- [dramatic music]
- [thudding]
[Leon]
Holy shit.
[flies buzzing]
Elephants.
They're fucking huge.
[whispering] Sarge. Sarge!
I don't like this.
We shouldn't fucking be here.
This. this doesn't feel right.
I'm telling you.
something's not right.
[suspenseful music]
This is what we do. Leon.
I picked you for a reason. man.
[sniffles]
- Hmm.
- All right.
- Rockslide.
- [shushes]
[loud breathing]
[whispers] It's asleep.
[loud breathing. grumbling]
[ominous music]
[whispers] God bless...
[whispering] Sir. what do we do?
[growling and screeching]
[growling]
- Run!
- Fuck!
[roaring]
Go!
[dramatic music]
[Baker grunts]
Move it. move it!
[gunshots]
Leon. come on!
Up here!
[grunting]
Down.
[Leon panting]
What the fuck was that?
[crashing and thudding]
[growls]
[roars]
- [grunting]
- [splashing]
[indistinct chatter]
- [Keyes] Fuck. man!
- Fuck this.
-Fucking dinosaurs...
-The fucking Flintstones. man.
This is. this is
fucking bullshit.
I didn't sign on
to kill fucking dinosaurs.
We gotta just keep
our shit together.
Best thing is to find
Baker and Leon
and get the fuck out
of Dodge ASAP.
Find Baker and Leon?
That's fucking bullshit. man.
I ain't going back into that
fucking cave of horrors
for no one or nothin'!
We gotta call
for emergency extraction
right fucking now!
Except Leon
was humping the radio.
- [birds chirping]
- [crickets chirping]
- Fuck!
- Well. we ain't nothing
but sitting bait here.
- Let's move!
- Which way?
- [thudding]
- Towards whatever's making
- all that goddamn noise.
- [Xavier] Move!
Towards it?
- [Keyes] Take point.
- [Xavier] Come on. move!
[ominous music]
- Fuck!
- [growling]
[grunting and groaning]
- [Baker] Oh. fuck.
- [groaning]
[panting]
There's a river
around here somewhere.
I saw it on the map.
If we keep heading down.
- we'll hit it.
- Can it swim?
- [snarling]
- [trees crashing]
- Gotta get there first.
- [both grunting]
[dramatic music]
[roaring]
- Find cover.
- [grunts]
- Come on!
- Fuck!
[roaring]
Over here. the tree!
Come on. move! Get down!
[snarling]
[panting]
[roars]
[snarling]
[suspenseful. ominous music]
[Leon speaks softly]
What are you doing?
- [explosion]
- [Baker] Go! Go. go. go!
[dramatic music]
[roars]
[Baker]
Come on. let's go!
Let's go!
[gasping]
[water splashing]
Fuck.
[crashing]
[roars]
You airborne qualified. Leon?
What?
[yells]
[roaring]
- [splashing]
- [muffled bubbling]
[gasping]
Leon!
Leon. Leon!
Fuck! [grunts]
Leon! [grunts]
Stay with me. brother.
[grunting]
Stay with me. Leon!
Of course you can swim.
-[yells]
-[in Russian accent]
Hey. Hey! Over here!
Hey!
- [both grunting]
- Follow me.
[grunting]
[snarling]
[roars]
- [grunting]
- [loudly sighs]
[panting]
- Leon. Fuck.
- Your friend. is he alive?
- [snarling]
- Come on. Leon.
- [breathing heavily]
- [somber music]
- Wake up. brother! Wake up.
- [coughs]
[Baker]
Get it out. Get it all out.
[coughs]
- Welcome back. brother.
- American?
Yeah. we're American.
Who the fuck is this?
[pants] My name is Sofia Wagner.
the woman who just
saved your lives.
thank you very much.
I have a place
over that way. my lab.
We should go there quickly.
We'll be safe there from the rex
and the flock of deinonychus.
- We should move.
- Rex?
As in. tyrannosaurus rex?
- [roaring]
- [shushes]
[ominous music]
[growling]
[roar]
[whispers]
How are you even here
if you don't know what that was?
That's the mother tyrannosaur
across the river.
They mate for life.
with the mother
raising the chicks
and the father hunting.
Without the father.
the mother will be forced
to take chicks
on the hunt with her.
The father will do
whatever it takes
to get back
to his territory and family.
We should be safe for now.
Listen. lady.
We're a recon team. seven men.
Got separated when we ran
into those fucking things.
We're not going anywhere else
until I find my team.
If your men are
on the other side of the river.
then they're likely
already dead.
You can take it from me.
and I'm never wrong. This way.
Or you can stay and die.
your choice.
- [birds chirping]
- [Sofia grunts]
["Run Through The Jungle
(John's Version)"
by John Fogerty]
Get up.
[grunting]
♪♪ Whoa. thought
It was a nightmare ♪♪
- [muted]
- ♪♪ Lord. it's all so true ♪♪
♪♪ They told me
Don't go walking slow ♪♪
♪♪ The devil's on the loose ♪♪
- ♪♪ Better run
Through the jungle ♪♪
- [grumbling]
♪♪ Better run
Through the jungle ♪♪
♪♪ Whoa. don't look back to see ♪♪
♪♪ Thought I heard a rumblin' ♪♪
♪♪ Calling to my name ♪♪
♪♪ Two hundred million
Guns are loaded ♪♪
- ♪♪ Satan cries. take aim ♪♪
- [hissing]
♪♪ Better run
Through the jungle ♪♪
- ♪♪ Better run
- [sniffing]
Through the jungle ♪♪
- [snarling]
♪♪ Whoa. don't look back to see ♪♪
[grumbling]
[panting]
[roaring]
♪♪ Over on the mountain ♪♪
♪♪ Thunder magic spoke ♪♪
♪♪ Let the people know... ♪♪
Guess it don't matter. X.
Where we headed?
We go northeast
until we hit the blue line.
- Looks like a klick or less.
- [birds chirping]
Them notes we found
had it marked
as Research Station Four.
- [rumbling]
- And what about. uh.
Sergeant Baker and Leon?
Baker got the same map.
If they're still alive.
they'll head
in the same direction.
Fucking Jericho.
He had to know something
like this was out here. right?
I doubt it. man. Uh. you know.
if they knew there were
dinosaurs out here.
he'd send an Arc Light strike
and turn this whole thing
into a goddamn parking lot.
I mean. he's a...
he's an evil prick.
but he's not stupid.
Except we're north of the Z.
You think Washington
would strike up here
on some intel of dinosaurs?
Think he'd think
that's as crazy as me.
[laughter]
You doin' all right. man?
Yeah. too much goin' on
to hear anything else.
[Keyes]
Well. that's good.
[Xavier]
Quiet down.
There's still NVA out here.
Fuckin' doubt that. man.
There were gooks out here.
It is fuckin' conch snacks now.
[Miller]
Goddammit. look
at all this dino shit.
- [grumbling]
- [Keyes] That's Eli's. [laughs]
[water lapping]
- [light suspenseful music]
- [panting]
- [birds chirping]
- Welcome to my home. gentlemen.
My home away from home
for one year.
seven months. 11 days.
Research Station Four.
Very good.
[growling and grumbling
in the distance]
There were more like us.
American soldiers.
-Green Berets.
-Green Berets?
What is this?
- [Baker] It's
the best men we have.
- Then they're probably dead.
It's all that happens
in this valley. death.
You survived.
Call me the lucky one.
[creaking]
Don't worry. this is
the safest place to be
in the valley.
Steel-reinforced concrete.
very thick walls.
four stories high on one side.
So now. you explain to me
why you are here.
I think you're the one
with some explaining to do.
[chuckles]
[Leon]
What is she doing?
[clears throat] Medicating.
[Leon]
What the fuck is she
putting in her arm?
Jesus fucking Christ! Sarge!
- [moans softly]
- What the fuck is going on?
[clattering]
What are you doing here?
Hmm?
What is the purpose
of this facility.
and why the fuck
are there dinosaurs outside?
[laughs] Oh. my God.
It is so great
to hear voices again.
I've been alone for so long.
Why? What happened?
General Borodin happened.
He killed everyone
who knew about this place.
Painted the walls
with their brains.
If everyone else is dead.
then what are you
still doing here?
I've been starving. hiding.
surviving with nothing else
to do but medicate.
[melancholic music]
You understand. don't you?
Leon. go see if you can get
a radio signal.
Now!
[clatter]
[Sofia]
Hmm.
How very Chekhov. Sergeant.
[chuckles] I saved your life.
Now. I wouldn't have needed
saving if it wasn't
for the supposedly
extinct dinosaurs.
Charlie Oscar Six.
this is Vulture Bravo Two. Over.
And I'm gonna bet
my old friend Viktor Charlie
- had nothing to do with that.
- [Leon] Charlie Oscar Six.
- this is
Vulture Bravo Two. Over.
- But you.
mysterious Russian
Little Miss Morphine.
you seem pretty good for it.
Oh. I am very good for it.
- There it is.
- [static]
Charlie Oscar Six.
this is Vulture Bravo Two. Over.
Borodin. what's his deal?
Why kill everyone?
It is the Russian way to protect
what he is doing here.
- [Baker] And that is?
- The collider.
The hell is that?
[ominous music]
Oh.
Oh. I don't think I want
to play this game. Sergeant.
Information is
the greatest commodity in war.
- and I can see
you've been deprived of it.
- Mm.
- [grunts]
- Why don't I ask you
20 questions
and see if you know
what the fuck
you are even doing here?
[Leon]
Sergeant.
I got the colonel.
- [static]
- Standby
for Vulture Bravo Actual.
- Over.
- [static]
[sniffs]
- Charlie Oscar Vulture.
-[Jericho] This is Six.
Vulture. send SITREP.
-[breathes deeply]
Requesting immediate Dust Off.
We've come under heavy fire
and mission is compromised.
I say again.
immediate Dust Off. Over.
Is the mission complete.
Sergeant Baker?
[sighs]
Six... [clears throat]
I'm gonna get this out
in plain language.
I don't know what
you really sent us
out here to find.
but we found
a fuck load more than
just some missing Green Berets.
There's some kind of
crazy Russian experiment
that's been going on out here.
Why don't you ask higher
about a general named Borodin?
Somehow. his team have brought
dinosaurs back to life.
and it was dinosaurs
that ate your Snakebite team.
Now. since we inserted.
we've been attacked
by all kinds of
prehistoric beasts.
all of them hungry. pissed off.
and chomping at the bit
for their little piece
of the American pie.
We need an emergency extract
from this fucking zoo.
and that's not an option!
Hey. l... li... listen to me.
Sergeant Baker.
Take a fucking breath.
all right?
And give me your position.
That's all I'm asking.
Fucking listen to me.
Five of my men are missing.
I'm gonna go find them.
dead or alive.
When I do.
I'll send a POS REP...
[dramatic music]
and we'll be bringing with us
one female Russian survivor.
- [breathes shakily]
- If you want her
to spell it out for you.
have the birds ready.
You think you can blackmail me.
you little son of a bitch?
You don't know. all right?
You've got one piece
in the puzzle. that's all.
If you want
that puzzle piece. Colonel.
then you will send evac.
LZ marked by flares by 22:00.
Sun's setting. Colonel. Out.
-Listen...
-[static]
I think they're
fucking delirious.
you hear... did you hear that?
Goddamn dinosaurs.
losing their fucking minds.
- eating the fucking mushrooms.
- Yeah. sounds
just about right. Colonel.
I'll fucking rip his skin off
and make ponchos out of him.
[chuckling softly]
Pawns. just pawns.
You are all just pawns
like I was.
That's my men
you're talking about.
and they're out there. lost!
Yeah. I know
where I would rather be.
You know all about these things.
How they operate
and where they're likely to be.
[suspenseful music]
See. you're on point. lady.
Get your ass up.
Pawns don't got a choice.
[clattering]
[door opens. creaks]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [man] Say again. over.
Any reason to believe
what he said?
I don't think so. Colonel.
I mean. we're out here
looking for some kinda
nuclear reactor or collider
that might be capable
of producing weapons-grade
nuke materials.
but... [scoffs] I mean.
million-year-old dinosaurs?
Yeah. but hold on. but he...
Baker's not crazy. all right?
So. w... why would he lie to us?
Anything's possible
when you start fucking around
with nuclear materials.
Yeah. Well.
we damn well better find out.
Check with your spook sources
about this Borodin character.
all right?
- I'll get right on it. sir.
- Let's go. Come on. Fuck off.
[indistinct chatter continues]
[tiger snarls]
[suspenseful. eerie music]
[growling]
- [crickets chirping]
- [dinosaurs grumbling]
- Look!
- [birds chirping]
They're harmless.
[chuckles softly]
Yes. Sergeant?
[water lapping]
We were attacked last night.
Little boys will play
as soldiers.
I ain't playing. I'm asking
your professional opinion.
Then. as professional courtesy.
I will answer.
It was fast and it was strong.
And it ambushed me clean.
It was covered in feathers.
I think.
It was at least
eight to ten feet tall.
Raptors. big ones.
A lot bigger
than specimens I've seen
for velociraptor or deinonychus.
I've counted six big ones
in the valley.
The most intelligent
of these monsters.
- Lady knows her stuff.
- Thank you.
It's what she's not telling us.
that I don't trust.
Trust is earned. Sergeant.
So far. I've saved your skins
and given you shelter.
Keep walking.
[dramatic tone]
Site Three is about
a klick up ahead.
[birds chirping]
Then we go west to Site Four.
Figure if Baker and Leon
are still alive.
they'll head there.
Another mile to go. guys.
[Miller]
Thank God.
It's fucking hot. Fuck! Fuck!
Yeah. the heat.
that's the problem here.
[Keyes]
Oh. fuck you. man.
[chuckles]
It's hotter than Miss July.
Baking me a cake
in the middle of a...
- [gasps]
- Oh. shit!
[gunshots]
[Xavier]
Southside left!
- Southside left!
- [groans] Fuck!
- [groans] Jesus!
- [Miller] What the fuck
is happening?
[gunshots continue]
Kill them all! No prisoners!
Keyes!
Fuck!
- [groaning]
- Keyes!
- [Miller] Can't see 'em!
- [Eli] Me neither.
- Oh. shit.
- [Xavier] Need to know
how many and where.
- What in hell is that?
- [gunshots in the distance]
That's AKs and M16s.
Sounds like our guys
in a firefight.
- With who?
- Let's go find out.
[indistinct shouting]
- Need to know
how many and where!
- [Keyes] Just came out
- of nowhere!
- [indistinct shouting]
- Logan!
- [Logan] I got him!
Can't see shit.
- Where are they?
- [Miller] Logan. goddammit.
-you can kiss Keyes later...
-[cross talk]
- [rattling]
- [gunshots continue]
- Get to work. man. You good?
- [Keyes groans]
- [explosion]
- [Tolstoy shouts] Keep firing!
- [groaning]
- [chuckles]
- Motherfucker. are you good?
- Almost blew my cock off.
-[Miller] Ah. yeah.
It's just circumcised. bro.
-[chuckles]
- Yeah.
- [explosion]
[gunshots continue]
[gasps]
- [whooshing]
- [grumbling]
[ominous music]
[rumbling]
- [Logan] Cease fire. cease fire!
- [Xavier] Cease fire!
- [Keyes groaning] Oh. it's bad.
- [Miller] You good?
I gotta put an...
No. it's not bad.
-[groaning] God...
-You gotta just lay down.
- Deep breaths.
- [grumbling]
[dramatic music]
[speaks indistinctly]
fucking damn it!
- Fuck.
- [gunshots]
[grumbles]
[music increases]
- [grumbling]
- [indistinct shouting]
[screaming]
Oh. they've got air support now.
That's. that's good.
Grab Keyes.
Stay low and head for the trees.
- [Miller] Gotta move on.
- [groans]
- [gunshots]
- [yells]
[panting]
[thud]
- [thud]
- [grumbles]
[grumbling]
- Fucking monster.
[music continues]
[groans. breathes heavily]
[man screaming]
-Oh. fuck. Fuck that. man.
-[Xavier] Keep moving!
Don't look back.
[Miller]
Don't look back. man.
Keep moving.
No. no. no.
No. no. no. Keep moving.
[roars]
[choking]
[roaring]
- [thud]
- [gasps]
Let's go. Come on.
[shouts] Run. Sergei!
Run!
- Fire!
- [gunshots]
[screeching]
[grunting and panting]
- [music continues]
- [yells]
Run. Sergei!
- [grumbling in the distance]
- [panting]
Only two of you now. huh?
Why you run away? Hmm?
What in hell are those things?
You just left us there.
[ominous music]
[indistinct muttering]
My job is to find GI.
not babysit you.
[speaks in Russian]
[Sergei speaks in Russian]
Let's go. let's go!
- Let's go!
- [breathes heavily. groans]
- Easy. easy.
- [thudding]
- We gotta get moving. Keyes.
- [Keyes groaning] Jesus.
- You good to go?
- [Keyes groans]
- [Logan] You okay?
- I've been shot. man.
in dinosaur Vietnam.
About 12.000 miles
and a million fucking years
from being okay.
[Logan]
Oh. you're gonna be okay. man.
God fucking Jesus!
[groaning] Oh!
Logan. when you're done
patching him up.
- take point and keep us
in the trees.
- [Logan] Yeah.
- Through and through. Keyes.
- [Keyes] Oh. fucking Jesus!
- Fucking... take it easy.
- Can these things smell blood?
- Eat shit.
- [Xavier] Zip it. Eli.
- [Baker] Check fire. Vulture.
- [gasps]
I'm coming through with Leon
and a hitchhiker.
[Miller]
Ah. damn. Baker! [laughs]
- Glad to see you alive
and kicking. man!
- Who's the chick?
SITREP. who's shooting at you?
What the fuck happened to Keyes?
I don't know and I have no idea.
Goddamn flappy fucking big bird
dinosaurs cleaned 'em up.
Took a round in Keyes' thigh.
He won't be easy to move now.
- Who's this?
- [Miller] Yeah.
Just someone who can help.
Listen. evac is inbound
and Sofia here
has a safe place to wait it out.
Let's get him patched up
and move.
And the skirt?
[panting]
She knows what's going on?
She knows more than we do.
She's our ticket outta here.
I prefer
to think of you as my ride.
Russians? Our ticket home
is a fucking Russian?
I'm born in East Berlin.
if that makes you
feel any better.
It doesn't. No fucking way.
not after
what we've been through.
So those guys out there
are fucking Russians
shooting at us? Not MVA?
Yeah. and there's likely
more of them out here.
- [softly] Jesus.
- [growling]
Whatever these things are.
they were stalking us
last night.
- [growling]
- [panting]
Sofia. ideas?
- [rustling]
- Deinonychus.
Pack hunters. They like to...
Half the pack on the ground
and the other half
in the treetops.
Watch for their sickle claws
on each toe.
What is she.
like a dinosaur freak?
A dinosaur super freak.
you stupid redneck
- fascist ass wipe.
- Jesus fucking Christ. lady.
I was just asking. is all.
Enough.
[screeching and growling]
[dramatic music]
Fire on anything that moves.
- [gunshots]
- [screeching]
[indistinct shouting]
Watch out! Watch out!
- [man 1] Xavier!
- [man 2] On your right!
[indistinct shouting]
They're in the trees. man!
[continues indistinctly]
-[screeching and roaring]
-[man 3] Fuck you!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
[Leon]
How many
of these things are there?
One shot. one kill!
[Miller]
Oh. fuck!
[man 2]
Look out. look out!
Take that.
Logan!
- Logan!
- Cease fire! Cease fire!
It got Keyes!
- Logan! Logan!
- Wait!
- You have to run fast
to catch him!
They will drag him
until they feel it's safe!
Fuck.
- Let's get after him. Go!
- Go. go. go.
- [growling]
- [Keyes shouts] Baker!
Fuck... get the fuck off me.
you little shit!
Get the fuck off me. Logan!
- [screeching]
- [grunting]
Fuck off! [grunts]
Where the fuck are you.
guys? Fuck!
- [music continues]
- [grunting continues]
[screeching]
[grunts]
- [screeching]
- [grunting]
[groans. grunts]
[snarling]
- [screeching]
- [blade rings]
[grunts and pants]
[snarling and screeching]
You goddamn fucking
murderous turkeys.
You coming at me?
You're gonna need fries
and fucking gravy.
[screeching]
[suspenseful music]
[panting]
[softly] Oh. yeah.
[loudly] Yeah.
That's what
I fucking thought. [laughs]
Ugh. fuck.
[panting]
It's so fucking hot.
Okay.
[lighter clicks]
[birds chirping]
- [soft growling]
- [ominous tone]
[screeching]
- [thudding]
- [gasping]
- [growls]
- [flesh squelching]
[dramatic music]
[choking]
- [flesh squelching]
- [gasping and choking]
- [Logan shouts] Keyes!
- [growling]
- [choking]
- [Leon] I swear I heard him.
- [Xavier] Keyes!
- [Logan] Keyes!
[indistinct chatter]
- [growls]
- [breathing heavily]
- [flesh squelching]
- [Xavier] Keyes!
[indistinct chatter]
- [blade rings]
- [screeching]
Oh!
- Light it up!
- [Miller] Oh. shit!
- [gunshots]
- [roaring]
- Cease fire!
- [Xavier] Cease fire!
[Keyes choking]
Keyes! Oh. shit!
- Keyes!
- [Eli] There he is!
- [indistinct chatter]
- [gasping and groaning]
- Oh. shit!
- Fucking help me here.
-Give me. give me...
-Miller. get in here!
- [Miller] I'm on it. Sarge!
- [cross talk]
- Eli. stand watch. Keep it on.
- Put pressure bandage...
Keep pressure on that.
Eli. stand watch.
- [cross talk]
- [crying and screaming]
- They tore
his fucking guts out. Sarge.
- [Keyes] Oh. Jesus! Oh. fuckin...
Looks like he's been...
he's been run through
a fucking meat grinder.
- Yeah. I know. [spits]
- [Keyes crying and screaming]
Miller. Miller.
Get that stretcher out.
- Leon!
- [Leon] Yeah.
Grab a couple of poles
to carry him back
to the research station
for evac.
Leave him. Those big raptors
will come back
with their full pack of six.
and when that happens.
we'll all die.
-If we leave him. we might
have chance of survival...
-I don't give two fucks
-how bad he's cut up.
He goes with us.
-[speaks indistinctly]
- [somber music]
- Vultures.
sun sets in half hour.
I do not wanna be
stumbling around in the dark
with Marlboro Man passed out
on the stretcher.
- Rig him in there
and let's roll.
- [crying continues]
- Here. You can have some weight.
- [Miller] Leon!
- [Keyes] ...God! Oh. my God!
- [Logan] More bandages.
more bandages.
- [cross talk]
- Stay on that.
- You're in the best
of hands. Keyes.
- Fuckin' hurts...
What you doing this
twice for in one day. man?
[crying] Oh. my God.
Best of hands. brother.
Best of hands.
- [thunder rumbling]
- [rain spattering]
[Xavier] Hurry up!
[Baker] Move. move.
move. move. move. Logan!
- Move. Logan! Move. Logan!
- [Keyes crying]
- [Baker] Get the door! Come on!
- [Sofia] ...at the door!
- [Leon] Got it.
- [Xavier] Move.
[cross talk]
- [papers rustling]
- On the table! On the table!
[Xavier]
Lay him down. lay him down!
[Logan]
Hey. Keyes. Keyes.
look at me. Look at me.
-[Baker] Get on that...
-[Logan] You're okay.
- [Eli] Fuck. Fuck. fuck.
fuck. fuck. fuck.
- [Baker] Keep the pressure
- on it.
- [cross talk]
[Sofia]
I've got the light!
-[Logan] Come on. Keyes...
-Miller. Eli.
Take perimeter.
Do an ammo count.
premise review.
- [Miller] On it. Sarge.
- [Logan] Look at me. Keyes.
- [Xavier] You'll be okay. Keyes.
- Leon!
- [Leon] Yeah.
- Cover for the sergeant.
- [Leon] I'm on it.
- [groaning]
-[Leon] Okay. okay...
-[Baker] Sarge...
-[Logan]
Breathe. breathe. Keyes.
- is there
anything else we can do for him?
He ain't gonna make it
much longer. Sarge.
- [Keyes groaning and crying]
- He's bleeding bad.
Maybe change the dressings.
but I... I... I don't know...
Get some morphine into him
and see what we can do
to stop the bleeding.
- Let's go.
- [cross talk]
[Keyes screaming and crying]
[Leon]
You gotta get
that morphine in right now.
- [Logan] Keyes. Keyes!
- [Leon] I got... I got th...
[breathes shakily]
[Logan]
Keep your eyes on me.
Eyes on me.
- [music continues]
- [groaning continues]
[Logan]
Come on... I'm coming.
Keyes. I'm coming in.
-I need you to calm down...
-[Leon] Okay. ready?
-[Logan] Keyes...
-[Leon] Here we go!
- [panting]
- We got any more?
- Where's the other one?
- [Baker] Get the morphine
into him!
- [cross talk]
- Where the fuck
is the other one?
Where's the second morphine?
- [Keyes screams]
- Here we go.
-Son of a bitch.
- feel that?
You feel that. man?
-Keyes. Hey. listen to me.
Take a deep breath.
-There you go...
[Leon]
Can you breathe?
That's good. that's better.
That's good. man.
- [cries]
- [Leon] I need you
to stay with me. man.
Hey. Hey. look at me.
[indistinct chatter
in the distance]
[clattering]
[thunder rumbling]
Just couldn't help yourself.
could you?
I did nothing to stop this.
What?
The dinosaurs.
We could've stopped it.
It was just accident.
[Baker]
An accident?
Why didn't you say this before?
[Sofia]
I wanted to.
but you are... [sighs]
- What?
- You are the enemy.
Lady. I'm not the one
trying to shoot you or eat you.
I know. I know. I see that now.
You are good men.
- You are all good men...
- [thunder rumbling]
but I needed
more than good men.
I needed someone who could stop
what is happening
in this valley.
[Xavier]
Baker. we need more eyes
on the perimeter.
- Leon. help the Sarge.
- [Leon] Yes. Sarge.
[Xavier]
Leon. cover that window.
Listen. My mission is
to get my men home.
not fight dinosaurs.
There won't be a home
if Borodin isn't stopped.
Look out there!
[exhales deeply]
Sofia. what exactly
was going on here?
[Logan softly]
It's all right. We got you.
- [suspenseful music]
- Put pressure...
My husband was
nuclear research scientist.
My field is paleontology.
We were sent here
by Soviet madman Borodin
to do what was
strictly research.
Nobody conducts
scientific research
in the middle of a jungle
in the middle of a war.
Even Russia didn't want
his research on home ground.
When you are ordered
to do something
by a man like Borodin.
you do it or you die!
[exhales sharply]
When we arrived. this collider
had already been tested.
We were told that
he was working on wormholes
so that Soviet Union
could crush America.
send tanks
onto White House lawn.
But my husband said
that Borodin...
- cut corners. you would say.
- [music continues]
Particles did not collide
and some elements slingshot
beyond speed of light.
[exhales sharply]
Wormhole... opened in the past
and dinosaurs walked through.
- [thunder rumbling]
- [exhales sharply]
I came with my husband
because of my knowledge.
[exhales deeply]
Best team.
[melancholic music]
Where's your husband now?
[crying] I was out
studying the herbivores
that came through.
Borodin wanted to... see
if he could make use
of the dinosaurs.
I heard cracking of machine guns
and came home... [sobs softly]
to find whole team dead.
Darling husband included.
And so I've sat here.
doing the only thing I can
to ease the pain.
We should have stopped him.
He just left his mess of lizards
and moved on to rebuild
another collider.
He won't stop.
Look at where
playing God got us.
- [thunder rumbling]
- [softly] Hmm?
I know.
[Baker]
You know where this
rebuilt collider is?
[sniffles] They entered
a river in the mountains.
He thinks I'm dead.
but I know about it.
You have to help me
make this right
or more people
will suffer the consequence.
[music continues]
- [Baker] How we looking?
- [Xavier] Uh. not good.
-[shushes. softly] It's okay.
It's okay. man. It's okay.
-[crying and whimpering]
- It's all right.
- [Keyes] I wanna go home.
[Logan]
We're gonna get you
back home. man.
What you gonna tell
your mama about this?
- [thunder rumbling]
- [screeching]
[roaring and sniffing]
[rain spattering]
- [Miller] You good?
- [sighs] Yeah.
[sighs] Yeah. these things
just freak me out. man.
You can handle it.
[Eli]
Yeah.
I'd handle it better
if I had me a drink.
Should've brought along
that lucky flask.
[Miller]
Baker catches you
with that flask in the field.
he's gonna jam it up your ass.
That little flask
saved my ass one time.
When you and I were
running for CAV.
before we went to the LURPs...
[light melancholic music]
we're clearing out
this little. uh.
this little
piss ant village... [sniffs]
Charlie jumped out
from behind a pile of bamboo
and just fucking nailed me
with one round from his SKS.
The round hit the flask
in my pocket. flattened it.
but all I got was
knocked in my ass.
If it hadn't been
for that flask in my pocket...
- That was God.
- [Eli] Mm.
But I remember well.
That what happened after that...
never gonna forget
those four people.
Gonna take more
than a whisky flask
- to save your ass this time.
- Yeah.
Gonna take more than God
to save yours.
Where is he?
He's not there.
You're here. They're here.
That's what I believe in.
[Miller]
You know why I carry
these beads every day?
I'm asking those people
we killed for forgiveness.
Nah. the fuckings...
Don't listen to me. man.
- I'm just fucked up.
- [Logan] Hey. you still
with me. Keyes?
- Keyes. wake up!
- [Xavier] What?
[Eli]
Keyes is gonna
fucking die for sure
if we don't get him
outta here. man.
[Miller]
He's gonna make it. [sniffs]
- [roaring in the distance]
- Hey. Sarge. we got movement.
[ominous music]
Shit. Need more time.
What's the ETA
on those choppers?
Last ETA was about an hour.
Fucking rotor heads
don't like flying at night.
- [Baker] Fuck.
- Can we hold for an hour?
They still out there.
just pacing the perimeter.
Logan. need you out here.
[Logan]
You're gonna get
to the other side of this.
- you're gonna be fine.
- Go. I got him.
- Hang in there. I'll be back.
- [Baker] Grab your left.
[thunder rumbling]
[roaring in the distance]
What's going on?
Let me know when you
got a target you can shoot.
[growling]
[softly]
He's just walking around.
[Baker]
You got a shot?
You want me to give away
our position?
They already know we're here.
- Lost it.
- Stay on it.
- Pretty smart for a bird.
- Way too smart for a bird.
Listen. man. I found out
some shit talking to the woman.
- [roaring]
- [shouts] Oh. shit.
they're inside!
- There's a bird!
- [roaring]
[gunshots]
[dramatic music]
[Xavier]
Get on it. Left. left.
Shit. it's here!
[Baker]
Go. go!
- [indistinct shouting]
- Miller!
- [man 1] Spread out!
- [man 2] Yeah! Let's go!
Left!
- Motherfucker!
- [Miller] Here.
here. here. here!
[man 3]
Cease fire!
Everyone. full mag.
[gun cocks]
It's probing us.
goddamn it. it's probing us.
[suspenseful music]
Eyes on. eyes on.
Quick as you can.
[thud]
[thudding]
[growling]
- [Baker] The fuck is that?
- Got it.
[gunshots]
[clinking]
- [screeching]
- [gunshots]
[dramatic music]
[yells] Fuck!
[Baker]
On your left! Whoa!
[shouts] Get out!
- [roaring]
- [yelling]
- [Baker] Fall back! Fall back!
- [Eli] Fall back!
[Baker]
Go. go. go. go! Go. go. go. go!
Leon. move!
[roaring and growling]
There are six in the flock
that came through!
They will find a way!
They always find a way!
Hey. don't worry about it.
Our chopper's
on its way. okay?
- [glass shatters]
- [Baker] Shit. Up top!
- [Xavier] Up. up!
- [Baker] Up top!
[gunshots]
- [thudding]
- [glass shatters]
- Son of a bitch!
- [indistinct shouting]
He won't survive an hour!
Your men still die!
- What would you have me do?
- There's a boat
on the docks outside.
- There's a boat there?
- Yes. it needs fixing.
that is not my skill.
Your men can.
Look. there's a escape hole
over there. the vents.
-Fuck...
-Trust me!
Open it. Everybody. we're
moving out through the vent!
Leon. give Sofia a hand.
Okay. we're gonna do
a new LZ. Keyes. okay?
-We're gonna move you to...
-[Keyes] I can't. I can't.
- Move. Keyes. Grab a leg.
- [Keyes] Put me in the corner.
- [Baker] Huh?
- [Keyes] Corner!
- Put me in the fucking corner.
- He wants to go in the corner.
[Logan]
No. no. no. no.
no. no. no. we...
- He wants to go.
- We...
- It's his decision.
- man.
-We're not doing...
-Three. two. one.
[Keyes groans]
Move it!
- [Logan] What are we doing?
- [Sofia] We need
to open this vent.
- [cross talk]
- God be with you. Keyes.
-God be...
-[Baker] Go. go. go. go.
[Sofia shouts]
Sergeant!
- Give me a grenade.
- I gotcha. I gotcha.
- I got you. I got you.
- Fuck no. man. Don't do this.
- Give me
a fucking grenade and go.
- [Baker] I got you.
- [thudding]
- [roaring]
[Xavier]
Let's go. let's go!
- [Sofia] Go!
- [Keyes breathing heavily]
-Man...
-Oh. my God.
[Logan] Baker.
You're not going anywhere
humping a fucking casualty.
- Be quick!
- [speaks indistinctly]
I can't do this
without you. man.
-Yeah. you can...
-I can't.
-The voices in my head...
- you fucking can!
- [crying]
- You fucking listen to me.
Th... they're trying to hurt you.
- [thudding]
- [roaring]
- You want a cigarette?
- [shakily] Yeah.
- Okay. Let's go.
- [crying]
[somber music]
[gasps]
Here you go. Enjoy that. Okay.
- [mumbles]
- [Baker] Logan!
[glass shatters]
You're a goddamn hero. man.
G... go. F... fucking go.
- Fucking go. man!
- [thudding continues]
[growling]
[roars]
Come get some.
you Foghorn Leghorn
motherfuckers.
- [music increases]
- [clinking]
[indistinct chatter]
[explosion]
[Baker]
All right. Let's get
this old lady started.
[Sofia]
The back. The back.
♪♪ That's one. two
Three. four. five ♪♪
♪♪ I'm psychotic. Keyes's alive ♪♪
Doesn't seem right.
leaving Keyes behind
with those lizard birds.
He's in God's good hands. man.
What's going on. man?
We heading north. Sarge?
Yeah. that's right.
Would you mind telling me why?
Vultures. let's bring it in.
[water lapping gently]
Listen. um...
Keyes was
a tough one to lose.
particularly knowing now
that we were sent here
on a bullshit mission.
But here we are.
in the deepest of shit.
Last comms with command said
they were sending chopper
as soon as we sent them
a POS REP for the extract.
We got maybe one shot
at that with what little
juice we have left in
our last radio battery.
That's one thing.
[light suspenseful music]
The other just might be
more important.
We stumbled
on some real nasty stuff.
Some Soviet shithead.
name of Borodin.
has been brewing
out here in the jungle.
It's a end-of-the-world shit.
and we just can't leave it.
Fuck yeah. we can!
We can do that in a heartbeat.
- End-of-the-world shit's
not our deal.
- The Sarge made the call. Eli.
we're already on the way.
How the hell can some
dipshit Russian dude
destroy the whole fucking world?
[Sofia]
You've all seen
what could happen.
and that was accident!
Again. that is not
our fucking business. Sarge.
Th... this is us
in the chain of command.
Here's where
end-of-the-world shit
gets sorted out.
That's presidents
and generals shit.
- That's Jericho level.
- Do you trust Jericho. Eli?
Do you trust him?
Maybe not Jericho. Sarge. but...
Nobody. Miller.
No god. no country.
no man should have
this fucking power!
This fucking thing
will make hydrogen bombs
look like Eli lighting
one of his farts.
[music continues]
I... I do have some pretty
powerful farts. Sarge.
- [growling in the distance]
- Shut the fuck up. man.
[chuckles]
This is worse.
- No man should have that power.
- Hmm. Damn straight.
Let's keep this
simple as possible.
given the circumstances.
We find it. tag it.
send in all the bombers we have.
No. No!
No. you can't do that.
You can't d...
- [thudding]
- Oh. fu... fuck.
Sarge. take the wheel.
- [Eli] What's wrong with her?
- She's dope sick.
Oh. good. We're following
a junkie in to hell.
[dramatic music]
[grumbling]
I said it right from the start.
there are monsters out here.
Thinking I'm crazy. don't you?
Y'all think I'm crazy.
but I knew. I told you all.
You fucking Baker. new kid.
all of you. told you.
[roaring in the distance]
-[grunts]
-Listen. focus on your job.
What was that?
[sighs]
That was just the father Rex.
Still looking for his family.
- [roaring continues]
- [sighs]
- You know that thing can swim.
- [chuckles] It's just animals.
We stay away from it.
it'll be fine.
What did you mean before.
that I can't do that?
[engine rumbling]
- Collider is unstable.
- [Baker] Right.
It throws off wormholes
like sparks.
Space and time are
same thing to wormhole.
You drop bombs on that.
you will be dropping bombs
all over the world instantly.
You ever say something
that doesn't take
a bad situation
and make it worse?
[light ominous music]
I'm Russian and you ask me this.
[scoffs]
So. what do we do?
You must go in and pull plug.
Do what?
- Literally. pull plug.
- And what if you're wrong?
I am never wrong.
[Miller]
Sarge. situation up here.
[roaring and grumbling
in the distance]
- What do you got?
- Over there.
It's just animals grazing.
We stay away from them.
we'll be fine.
[grumbling]
[Miller]
Think they're harmless?
[splashing]
Oh. fuck. Shit!
[Baker]
We stay the course. Xavier.
- Hey. hey. put that down!
- No. I need it!
-Fucking drop it. Fucking drop...
-I need it. give it to me!
- [Eli] Let go of that. lady!
- I need the morphine.
[screams]
[roaring]
- [splashing]
- [dramatic music]
Get on that.
[gunshots]
The fuck was that?
[muffled growling]
- [breathes shakily]
- You need to get
your shit together
'cause we're doing
what you want.
And we're probably all gonna die
screaming because of it.
Can we talk about that
screaming and dying bit?
Hey. hey. focus.
- What was that?
- [Sofia breathing shakily]
Spinosaurus.
Uh. we have to. to hurry.
[Miller]
You need me to tie her up?
Smoke these. Hmm?
Cope. the American way.
- [softly] Yeah.
- [Baker] No.
I think she's gonna be
just fine.
Right?
[gunshot]
- Son of a bitch. stay on that.
- What. they can
fucking swim now?
Should've seen 'em fucking fly.
[gunshot]
[exhales deeply]
- [suspenseful music]
- [grumbling in the distance]
[Logan]
Breathe. Relax.
Aim. Squeeze.
[roaring and grumbling]
[Logan softly]
Relax. Aim. Squeeze.
- [gunshot]
- Logan. shut it down.
Squeeze.
I hate 'em. [chuckles]
[Miller]
Logan. it's okay. Stand down.
Okay.
[breathes deeply]
[Logan]
Okay.
I'll shut it down.
I'll sh... I'll shut it down.
[light melancholic music]
I'll shut it down.
[exhales softly]
Yeah. You can all go.
I am gonna go.
-I...
-[Baker] Hey. hey.
hey. hey. Hey. dude.
[exhaling sharply]
You t... you told me
to shut it down.
- Yeah. it's not
your time. brother.
- I was just...
- Hey. It's not your time.
- What?
- No? Are you sure?
- No. Yeah. I need ya.
- I feel...
- We need you.
I can't feel anything.
I can't feel anything anymore.
- Okay. Yeah.
- Huh?
Yeah.
I can do this.
Yeah. I know.
- I know.
- Yeah. I'm good.
[breathes loudly]
[music increases]
[inhales sharply. groans]
Make it stop.
Stay hydrated.
- [grunts]
- [Baker speaks indistinctly]
Think the sergeant likes her?
[Sofia]
The drug
must leave your system...
The sergeant's
just doing his job.
can guarantee you.
dinosaurs have ventured
into Cambodia. In months.
they could be in Burma.
in China. in India.
Once they run out of food
in jungle.
where do you think
they're going to go to eat?
We'll stop them.
- [Sofia] Huh.
- You ready for this?
[sighs] Face my past?
Not really.
[light melancholic music]
Just smile. pull the trigger.
the problem goes away.
It's also the American way.
[whistles]
["Revolution Road" by Easton]
♪♪ Another small-town boy
Plucked away from his home ♪♪
♪♪ Revolution. revolution road ♪♪
♪♪ This evil war machine
Will make you beg
On your knees ♪♪
♪♪ Now pull the trigger. son
You're fresh outta 17 ♪♪
♪♪ Go hang up
On the president's phone ♪♪
♪♪ Revolution. revolution road ♪♪
♪♪ They don't give a damn '‘‘bout
The crooks and the thieves ♪♪
♪♪ Let's burn it down
Take a "no" for your sympathy ♪♪
♪♪ We won't back down
Til freedom is found ♪♪
- [roaring]
- [vocalizing]
♪♪ We will bow down
When peace comes around ♪♪
[vocalizing]
♪♪ We won't back down
Til freedom is found ♪♪
[vocalizing]
♪♪ We will bow down
When peace comes around ♪♪
[vocalizing]
[splashing]
[grumbling and roaring
in the distance]
[crickets chirping]
Fuck.
This looks painfully familiar.
- [ominous music]
- [flies buzzing]
Should've stayed
on the damn boat.
You sure it's this way. comrade?
It's this way.
- We push through.
- [softly] Oh. God.
I hate doing that.
- [growling in the distance]
- [grunting and sighing]
- [dramatic music]
- [screeching]
- [Xavier] Oh!
- [Logan] Sarge! Oh. fuck!
- [Baker] Behind you!
- [yelling]
- [indistinct shouting]
- [gunshots]
[man 1]
They're fuckin' everywhere.
- Fuck off me!
- [growling and screeching]
- [Sofia shouting]
- [screeching]
[grunting]
[groans. grunts]
[indistinct shouting continues]
[yelling]
[blade rings]
- [groans]
- [muffed gunshots and shouts]
[music increases]
[yells]
-Come and get me!
Come and get me!
-[man 2 shouts] Logan!
- [Xavier] Guys. we gotta move!
- Logan!
- [gunshots]
- Take the squad.
I'll go after Logan.
Come on!
- Come and get me!
- [splashing]
Fuck. Shit.
- [gunshots]
- [screeching]
I'm done with all you fuckers!
Get out of my head
with this shit...
[continues indistinctly]
- [screeching]
- Fuck.
[indistinct shouting]
[yells. laugh]
- [somber music]
- [screeches]
[Keyes]
You're a goddamn hero. man.
Thank you. Keyes.
- [exhales sharply]
- [gunshot]
[screeching]
[music increases]
[thunder rumbling]
- [static]
- [Baker] We have a visual
on the compound.
Standby to copy. Grid 197545.
- How copy? Over.
- Solid copy.
Say ETA for the extract.
Uh. 30 mikes.
Uh. tell the pilots
to look for a big ass fire
and a pile of rubble
at the grid I just sent.
[chuckles] Negative. Vulture.
That is now
a national security site.
Do not damage or approach it
in any way.
All right? You know
who you're dealing with?
I ain't McNeil. all right?
Yo... you understand
what I'm saying. Vulture?
I'm losing the radio. Six.
I copied.
approach and destroy the site.
We'll be standing by
for inbound choppers
and a side of fries.
Vulture out.
Don't get fucking cute
with me. Hey!
- [static]
- Hey!
I will personally crucify
that motherfucker.
You might wanna think
that over. Colonel.
A man who saves the world
from a swarm of dinosaurs
- might just be a hero
to some folks.
- Not if anyone
hears about it. all right?
Fuck. I need. I need.
uh. escorts fueled up
and armed to the fucking teeth.
all right?
We're gonna show 'em
what millions of years
of evolution accomplishes.
Might be better
that site get destroyed
than let that stuff fall
into any hands.
Ours or theirs.
Yeah. well. you pussies
better get fueled up
and get ready.
[tense music]
Leon. you still got
the demo kits?
- Yes. sir.
- Outstanding.
Rig at least three full charges
at the base of the site.
Dig 'em in. I wanna see
that fucking structure collapse
- when they blow. Miller. Eli.
- [Miller] Sir.
Find and rig
any shipments outside.
And Xavier. find high ground.
Cover me when I move inside
and pull the plug.
Plug. Sarge?
You even know where to look?
I know. I will go
with Sergeant Baker.
[Baker]
Drop pack. let's go.
Miller.
Grenade.
You reckon the colonel's
really gonna send the choppers?
You just pissed him off enough
to make him forget about it.
-He'll send them.
He owes me that much.
-[thunder rumbling]
Sarge. who is McNeil?
McNeil was the original
leader of Vulture Squad.
Picked me fresh out of ROTC.
- And he was everything
a leader should be.
- What happened to him. Sarge?
Long story short.
he got fucked over by Jericho.
And he took the fall
on a failed airstrike mission.
We...
We lost most of the unit.
McNeil got a discharge
and I wound up in hospital
with a lot of dead brothers
on my conscience.
[somber music]
And shit. I got
a lot of live ones too.
I don't know about you.
Vultures. ma'am.
but I'm about ready
to bring it all on home.
- Cool.
- Let's get to work.
[dramatic. inspirational music]
[speaking in Russian]
[electricity crackling]
[upbeat suspenseful music]
[thunder rumbling]
- [thudding]
- [groaning]
[panting]
[indistinct chatter]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
[thudding]
Good fucking shit.
[speaking in Russian]
- [blade rings]
- [groans]
[thudding]
[thunder rumbling]
[in Russian accent]
The dogs of war.
you have returned just in time.
- One more test run tonight.
- Your big machine is in there?
[light ominous music]
It is.
What's it do?
I wouldn't expect you
to understand.
[Con Nhen]
So. my dealings with you...
all done?
[Borodin]
Just so. my dear.
- [continues indistinctly]
- [speaking in Russian]
and I wish you good luck
in striking the Yankees
out of the skies
over your homeland.
You have turned my homeland
into dinner for monsters.
[man speaking in Russian
in the distance]
[Borodin speaking indistinctly]
- That's Borodin.
- I know those men.
Did you know
of the monsters out there?
Mere beasts. not monsters!
Beasts of burden...
They must be the men
who ambushed your team.
And now they're questioning
their allegiance.
Where are Americans?
Dead by now.
Nothing can survive out there.
Trying to talk Borodin
into more caution.
saying dinosaurs might wind up
in the Red Square.
[Baker]
Is there any chance he'll stop?
Nyet. Borodin used them
like he used me.
The only monsters
I released in this valley
are men like you.
You were told to fetch
and you happily went
out there looking to kill.
- You madman!
- [speaking in Russian]
- Do it.
You are a threat to history.
To the people.
[ominous music]
We need to find a way in there.
Come on.
[gunshots in the distance]
[loudly] With me! Now!
- [dramatic music]
- [screeching in the distance]
Americans.
General. I found this one
sniffing around the camp.
There was another one.
but he hid in the trees.
What is this thing. General?
You fool.
Don't you know
what you have done?
[man speaking in Russian]
- [grunting]
- [thudding]
[indistinct chatter]
[speaking in Russian]
Shut the fuck up.
Okay.
I'm the one that helped
Borodin with dinosaurs.
This all needs to end
or he will destroy everything.
The asshole needs to be stopped.
Do you wanna join us?
- Da. We will.
- Da.
- We got incoming.
- [Sofia] Incoming?
Yeah. big incoming.
[thunder rumbling]
[suspenseful music]
What is this thing. General?
Get rid of it.
- [growling]
- [soldiers gasps]
[indistinct chatter]
[shushes]
[softly] Don't shoot.
[snarling]
[roaring]
- [gunshots]
- [indistinct shouting]
[dramatic music]
- [clanking]
- [roaring]
- [screaming]
- [squelching]
[thudding]
[screaming]
- [gunshots]
- [roaring]
- [shouting continues]
- [clanking]
[screaming]
[roaring]
[man shouting in Russian]
[music continues]
[roaring in the distance]
- [crashing]
- [glass shattering]
[growling]
[both roaring]
[gunshots]
[shouting
and screaming continue]
- [roaring]
- [screaming]
[engine rumbling]
[shouting in Russian]
- [groaning]
- [screaming]
Go! Get inside!
[thunder rumbling]
[Baker]
Let's go.
- [roaring]
- [helicopter blades whirring]
[gunshots]
[roaring]
Target on the move.
[Borodin]
out of my way!
[shouting in Russian]
[Baker muffled]
Okay. let's move.
[Leon breathes loudly]
Fuck. fuck.
[shouts] You sure
about this. Sarge?
- [roaring]
- [shouting]
[indistinct yelling]
[Baker]
This way! This way!
[cross talk]
Back. back. back. back!
[roaring]
- Go! Go. go!
- Go. go. go!
Move. move!
[Sofia]
Follow me. Sergeant!
- Here. here.
- [Leon] Inside. inside. inside!
- [roaring]
- [thudding]
We go now!
- Wire the collider.
- [speaks in Russian]
Do not wait for my command.
- [continues indistinctly]
- [cross talk]
[gunshots]
[Eli shouts]
Miller!
[explosion]
Miller. where are you?
- [dramatic music]
- [indistinct shouting]
- [groans]
- Demon!
You demon! [grunts]
American demon!
You kill my family!
[both grunting and groaning]
- [speaks in Vietnamese]
- [blade rings]
- [groans]
- [grunts]
[shouts]
- [grunting]
- [blade ringing]
[roaring]
- Oh. shit.
- [gasps]
[gunshots]
[Eli shouts]
Miller!
[chatter in Russian]
- [gunshots]
- [groans]
- [thudding]
- [whirring]
- Anyone else wanna be a hero?
- [Tolstoy] Hands up!
'Cause this will be
a real quick conversation.
[speaks in Russian]
The collider is still charging.
could go off any minute.
Get on it.
Leon. take the Russkies.
Keep planting the C4
and rig whatever else you can.
- Leave nothing behind.
- Let's go.
- [indistinct chatter on PA]
- [gunshots]
[roaring]
[thudding and crashing]
[Miller]
Please. forgive me.
No forgiveness!
- [yelling]
- [blade ringing]
Miller!
[groaning]
- [blade rings]
- You will die.
but we will rebuild!
God. forgive me.
God. forgive me!
- [dramatic. somber music]
- [echoing explosions]
- No!
- [clicks]
[explosions]
Miller!
[both grumbling]
- [alarm buzzing]
- Hey! I thought
all you had to do
was pull the plug.
It's too late.
It's set to automatic discharge.
I have to take console apart
and do a rewiring.
- How long is that gonna take?
- F... a few minutes. Then finish.
- Focus.
[speaking in Russian]
- [rumbling]
- [electricity crackling]
- Sofia.
- Don't worry.
Husband taught me fail-safes
and I'm never wrong.
Oh. I... I hope.
[whirring]
[dramatic music]
Vulture One. Vulture One.
Father Vulture. How copy. over.
Vulture. can you hear me?
This is Six.
Listen to me. all right?
I want that compound
secured and untouched.
You understand me? Hello.
Mother fuck... Hello!
Goddammit! What the fuck?
All this fucking work
for nothing.
You don't understand me!
You gotta secure the perimeter.
you fucks!
Fuck!
- Eli coming through!
- [Baker speaks indistinctly]
Xavier too!
[pants]
[Baker]
Where's Miller?
[melancholic music]
Miller's dead. man.
Leon standing by
with the last demo charge.
- Do you want him to blow it?
- You don't want to do that.
[ominous music]
Oh. you don't know me at all.
Think about what you could do
with all this power
and my knowledge. Hmm?
I've seen enough of your power
and your knowledge.
- [Borodin] Sofia.
- [crackling and rumbling
continue]
I guess all is fair
in love and war.
- [chuckles]
- Oh.
You cannot trust this woman.
She is fucking traitor.
- [gunshots]
- [groans]
[Borodin]
Oh. fuck.
[panting]
[softly] Your husband.
he cry like baby.
[grunts and cries]
[softly] Do it.
[melancholic music]
They were all better men
than you.
[spits]
- Is it done?
- [sighs] I've done it.
[rumbling increases]
[tense music]
- [grunts]
- [machine shuts down]
[Sofia sighs]
[Baker]
Fuck's going on?
[machine rebooting]
[Xavier]
Baker. need you here!
Son of a bitch.
Oh. fuck.
[screeching. growling]
[ominous music]
[Xavier]
You said there were only
six of them that came through.
Da. depending if Keyes
killed them on his way out.
[roaring]
[thunder rumbling]
Maybe I could have been wrong.
What the fuck?
[screeching]
[indistinct shouting]
[roaring]
[man whimpering]
- Holy shit!
- We need to blow
this shit up now.
Gotta get outta here first!
Sarge. pop smoke
and get everyone top side.
Top side? This is the only exit.
No. there is other side
of collider.
Pop smoke. Eli.
- [grunts]
- [clinking]
- Leon. C4 good to go?
- Oh. yeah. good to go.
[Baker]
Rig the blow.
- Frag out.
- Frag out!
- Fall back.
- [gunshots]
- [screeching]
- Fall back!
[dramatic music]
Fall back! Go. go. go!
[screaming]
[indistinct shouting]
Run. Sergei!
- [clanking]
- [screeching]
Claymore! Set up!
[Leon]
Setting. Sarge!
- [whirring]
- [softly] Come on. Fire.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
[snarling]
[chuckles]
- [yells]
- [blood spattering]
[explosion]
[Sofia]
Okay. [breathing heavily] Uh.
- [Baker] Fresh mags.
- [Xavier] Ready.
- [grunts]
- You're a vulture now.
[Xavier]
Where the fuck are we going?
That way.
[dramatic music]
[panting]
[explosions]
[roaring in the distance]
[screeching]
[Baker]
Pick it up. pick it up!
[indistinct shouting]
Move. move! Let's go!
[gunshots]
[indistinct shouting]
- [Baker] Keep going. keep going!
- [gasps]
- Next one.
- [roaring]
[indistinct shouting]
- [Sofia] Go! Go!
- [Xavier] Go. go. go.
Move. move. Go. go. go. go.
- Holy shit! [groans]
- [screeching]
Help me! [whimpers]
[roaring]
- [indistinct shouting]
- [gunshots]
[screeching]
- [Baker] Eli!
- Help me. God!
[grunting]
[Eli]
Don't leave me.
[Baker]
Come on buddy.
Don't let me dying. Sarge.
- [Sofia] Let's go!
- Eli!
He's gone! He's gone! Let...
Let... Let's go! Sergeant!
- [indistinct shouting]
- [yells]
[Baker]
Now. Leon!
Get up there. Focus!
-You look after her.
You have to...
-No...
- Go now.
- [clanking]
- [screeching]
- [gunshot]
You're not killing
any more of my men.
[gunshots]
Come on! Come on!
[roaring]
[dramatic music]
[gunshots]
[helicopter blades whirring]
Spread out! Spread out!
Let's go. 180.
- [indistinct shouting]
- [Xavier] Let's go! Let's go!
I need a SITREP. Sergeant!
- [roaring]
- [Xavier] Let's go!
What the hell was that?
Dinosaurs. sir.
[roaring]
Where's Baker?
I wanna see that son of a bitch.
He's not coming!
- [Jericho] Open fire!
- [gunshots]
[indistinct shouting]
[music continues]
- [Jericho] Eat that!
- [yells]
[screeching]
[Jericho on radio]
Incoming.
Stop this fucking shit!
Hang on!
- [gunshots continue]
- [screeching]
[shouting echoes]
[music continues]
[clinks]
- [explosion]
- [grunts]
Come on. fuckers.
[screeching]
- [clinks]
- Keep it coming.
[explosion]
[echoing screaming]
[screeching]
[groans]
[roaring]
[yells]
[echoing] Colonel. we need
to get the fuck out of here!
[screams]
- [grunting]
- [screeches]
[grunting]
[music increases]
- [blade rings]
- [screeches]
Load up!
[gunshots continue]
[roaring]
[muted]
- [whimpering]
- [laughs]
[explosion]
[grunting]
[music continues]
[laughs]
[loud explosions]
[whirring]
- [distant explosions]
- [gentle music]
[grumbling]
[roaring]
[whirring]
What the hell was
that shit show back there?
We're supposed to seize
the technology. not destroy it.
I guess you got
some explaining to do. sir.
It's all about escalation.
It's not gonna end
with the destruction
of that fucking machine.
No. It won't. Look!
[suspenseful tone]
[grumbling]
[light inspirational music]
Did you know. Colonel?
Know about all this?
- That's classified.
- Just tell us the fucking truth!
Truth is what I tell you.
all right?
Well. you wanna know
that the war could end
with that down there?
That the world could end?
- [indistinct chatter on radio]
- Colonel! You need to hear this!
[soldier on radio]
We're getting overrun here.
It looks like
giant goddamn lizards.
What the hell's going on?
[indistinct shouting]
[man shouts]
Hurry up let's move!
Go. go. go! Come on! Let's go!
-Hey. check this out...
-[cross talk]
Hey. get over here!
Check this out!
Holy cow!
[cross talk]
Come on. check this out!
[music increases]
[grumbling]
[indistinct chatter]
- Shit.
- [chuckles]
["Gimme Some Lovin"
by The Spencer Davis Group]
[chuckles softly]
♪♪ Hey ♪♪
♪♪ Well. my temperature's
Rising and my feet left
The floor ♪♪
♪♪ Crazy people knocking
'Cause they're wanting
Some more ♪♪
♪♪ Let me in. baby
I don't know what you got ♪♪
♪♪ But you better take it easy
This place is hot ♪♪
♪♪ And I'm so glad we made it ♪♪
♪♪ So glad we made it
I want you ♪♪
♪♪ Gimme some loving ♪♪
[man on TV]
The president this morning
addressed the press
about the presence of dinosaurs.
That's right. Dinosaurs.
In the South East Asian warzone.
[muted]
♪♪ Hey ♪♪
♪♪ Well. my head's exploding
And I'm floating to sound ♪♪
♪♪ Too much is happening
'Cause you're around ♪♪
♪♪ It's been a hard day
And nothing went too good ♪♪
♪♪ I'm gonna relax
Like everybody should ♪♪
♪♪ And I'm so glad we made it ♪♪
♪♪ So glad we made it ♪♪
♪♪ I want you
Gimme some lovin' ♪♪
♪♪ Gimme some lovin' ♪♪
♪♪ Gimme some lovin' every day ♪♪
♪♪ Hey ♪♪
♪♪ Well. I feel so good
Everything is getting hot ♪♪
♪♪ You better take the time off
'Cause the place is on fire ♪♪
♪♪ Better stop living
'Cause I have someone to do ♪♪
♪♪ We made it. baby
And it happened to you ♪♪
♪♪ And I'm so glad we made it ♪♪
♪♪ So glad we made it ♪♪
♪♪ Higher ♪♪
♪♪ Gimme some lovin' ♪♪
♪♪ Every day ♪♪
- ♪♪ Every night ♪♪
- ♪♪ Gimme some lovin' ♪♪
- ♪♪ Whoo-hoo ♪♪
- ♪♪ Gimme some lovin' every day ♪♪
- ♪♪ Gimme some lovin' ♪♪
- ♪♪ Hey. hey. baby ♪♪
- ♪♪ Whoo-hoo ♪♪
- ♪♪ Gimme some lovin' ♪♪
♪♪ Come on. every day ♪♪
♪♪ Gimme some lovin' ♪♪
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
[somber music]
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
[somber music]
[music fades]
[muted]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm